Were you sisters?
お 姉 妹だった?
Yeah, you.
うん、あんた
It's big, isn't it?
大きいんだよね
Oppa
おっぱ
Isn't it bigger?
い もっと大きくないだろうか?
think.
思う
What is the ideal?
理想は何か?
Ideal F.
理想F
It's too big.
デカすぎだろ
We still have C, right?
今だってCはあるでしょ?
good.
いい
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Molding, molding.
成形だ、成形
picture?
え?
It's Hokyo.
宝京だ
It's Hokyo sheets.
宝京シーツだ
Hit just the chikubi, make the chikubi bigger
チクビだけ打ちまくって、 チクビだけボイアントン大きくして
There is a scene called F cup.
F カップというシーンがある
While molding, everyone sucked on the chikubi,
成形しながら、 みんなでチクビ吸いまくって、
This is how Chikubi turns out, and if you make fun of him, Chikubi will end up like this.
チクビがこうなって、 ボッキしたらチクビがこうなっちゃう
It's hard.
き つい
Chikubi becomes like this.
チクビがこうなっちゃう
It was about LG21.
LG21くらいだったの
It becomes an F cup.
Fカップになっちゃう
F cup.
Fカップ
You put on your tights.
タイツこっちかけたでしょ
I don't like it.
嫌だな
Isn't it just a normal song?
普通の曲じゃないの?
I did it once and it was good.
一回やったしいいもんね
If you want to do it, you can do it.
やろうと思ったらできるじゃん
I love you already.
もう大好きなの
I love guessing things like this, right?
こういうの当てながら、 クシホラにすんすきでしょ
I feel like I'm going to sleep.
寝ちゃうみたいな
While applying it to your crotch.
股間に当てながら
There definitely is, right?
絶対あるでしょ
Because there isn't.
ないから
You've probably seen Pink Loader here before.
ピンクローダーここになって見たことあるでしょ
There isn't.
ないよ
Don't do it, then.
やるすんなよ、そしたら
You could say that their strengths are different.
どっちか、 強さが違うって言えるでしょ
This one is stronger.
こっちが強い
I put a pink loader on both chikubi.
両チクビに、 ピンクローダー当ててる
It jiggles.
プルプルする
You were licking this place.
ここ舐めてたでしょ
You were licking this area, weren't you?
この辺舐めてたでしょ
Hey.
ねぇ
I'll drop anything that moves.
動いちゃうのを落としてやるからね
It's okay if it's due to force majeure.
不可抗力ではいいよ
It's about enduring.
耐えるという、ほら
Please, please.
どうぞなんだから
picture?
え?
This way, right?
こっちでしょ
cold.
冷たい
Lick.
舐め
Because I don't lick it.
舐めないから
Not the smell.
匂いじゃなくて
It's getting harder and harder.
どんどん固くなってんじゃん
Woohoo.
うぅぅぅ
Uuuuuuuu.
うぅぅぅぅ
Kinkley Bock.
キンクリーボック
There are two kinks.
キンクは2つ
Rotor dog is stiff.
ロータードッグはチクが固まってるよ
Haha, it's stuck.
あはは、固まってるよ
There's a lump stuck in the rotor.
ローターにチクが固まってるよ
Hey.
ねぇ
Instagrammable.
インスタ映え
Ahahahaha.
あはははは
It's completely different, you know.
全然違うじゃん、ほら
Look.
ほら
Look, this one is getting harder and harder.
ほら、こっちがどんどん固くなってくる
What should I do if I don't come back?
どうしよう、戻んなくなったら
Look.
ほ ら
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
ほらほらほらほらほら
It hardens.
固 まってくる
Uuuuuuuu.
う ぅ ぅぅ
Right away, Lee?
さっそく、リーか
These pants and Meizugi.
このパンツとメイズギを
Understood.
わかった
I'll put one in.
1個入れちゃう
Help me.
手伝って
Ah, it was in.
あ、入ってた
Help me.
手伝って
it hurts.
痛い
it hurts?
痛い?
It's coming in, it's coming in.
入った、入ってくる
Please put it further back.
も っと、もっと奥に置いてください
No, it's fine.
いや、 いい
pain
痛
stomach.
い
Do you understand?
わか る?
I understand.
わかる
Okay.
よし
Put on your pants.
パンツを入れて
copper?
どう?
Inside and outside.
中と外
good.
良い
not good?
良くない?
good?
良 い?
Yeah.
うん
Did you put it in again?
また、入れた?
Post a photo.
写真を貼って
I don't know though.
わかんないけど
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Leave it in and put on your pants.
入れたまま、パンツと
With a pussy and panties.
おまんこと、パンツと
Leave the load on.
ロードを入れたまま
Are you angry?
怒ってんの?
dangerous.
あぶない
Well then, okay.
じゃあ、いい
Are you angry?
怒 って んの?
Leave the load on.
ロードを入れたまま
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
Ah, yes.
ああ、 そう
ああ、そう
Ah, that's it.
ああ、それね
That feels good.
それ、気持ちいい
That's it.
それね
That feels good.
気持ちいい、それ
That's amazing.
すごいよ
Hey, pin, pin.
ちょっと、ピンでピンで
Who taught you this?
誰に教えてもらったの?
I haven't been taught.
教えてもらってない
Are you trying to let me go?
行かせようとしてるの?
Yeah.
うん
There, there.
いた、いた
It's intentional, right?
わざとでしょ
You like it hard, right?
固いの好きでしょ
yes.
はい
This is suspicious.
これ、怪しいよ
If you're doing this much, can't you just do it every time?
こんなにやってたら、毎回やっててもらえない?
That's a lie, it's not that bad.
嘘、あんまやんない
No way.
やだよ
That's one thing.
そういうものは一つ
Men like this kind of thing, right?
こういうやつ、男性の好きでしょ
If you do something like this to a man.
男の人にこういうやつをすれば
Oh, are you going to do both?
あ、両方やるの?
I thought I was running away, but my weaknesses were revealed more and more.
逃げてるつもりがどんどん弱点が出る
I'm dying, after all.
死んじゃいますよ、これじゃあ
Who taught you that much?
誰がそんなに教えたの?
No, just a little.
いや、ちょっと
Is this area also a target of attack?
この辺も攻撃対象かな?
Is this even the target of attack?
この辺まで攻撃対象なの?
This is the whole body.
これ全身じゃん
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、やばい
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Is this my entire body?
これ、俺全身清観体なの?
Seriously?
マジか
Isn't this dangerous?
これ危険じゃない?
Not dangerous at all.
全然危険
This is terrible.
やばいよ
Hey, it's terrible.
ちょっとさ、やばいよ
Even if something like this happens to me.
こんなことされても
Is it just barely?
ギリギリなの?
Why not?
しないの?
this.
これ
Once you do it, they'll tell you to do it.
一回したらやってって言われるでしょ
scared.
怖い
I'm just touching it.
俺 ちょうど触っちゃってる
Isn't that what it is?
あれじゃないですか
It's a metamorphosis, and it's a treatment.
変態中、治療だ
治療
Do you all understand this when you do this?
これ、みんなこれやったら分かってる?
You'll be asked to do more, right?
もっとやってって言われちゃうでしょ?
Can't read?
読めない?
What do you think?
どうなの?
I'm not the kind of person who puts this much pressure on his crotch.
股間にこんなに当ててる人じゃないし
I'm doing it.
やって る
Get some sleep.
ちょっと寝てほら
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Take off your panties.
パ ンティを脱いで
パ ンティを脱いでほら
So, what about one?
で、1個は?
It's in, right?
入 ってるでしょ?
Put your feet down for a moment.
ちょっと足を置いて
Is the power on?
電源入ってるの?
The power is on, right?
電源入ってるじゃないですか
Is this the max?
これがマックスか
Is this Max?
これ が マ ック スか
I think it's in there.
入 ってるんじゃないですか
Let's expand it a little.
ちょっと広げてみせ
Let's spread it out.
広げてみせ
with your own hands.
自分の両手で
Let's take a look at the moment they are born.
ちょっと生まれる瞬間見ましょう
Why the moment of birth?
なぜ生まれる瞬間?
A cute pink child.
可愛いピンクの子供が
Will it be born?
生まれるの?
Let's watch the moment they are born.
生まれる瞬間見ましょう
Please wait a moment.
ちょっと待ってください
It's quite deep inside.
結構奥まで入ってますね
Have you remembered?
思い出てきた?
The sound.
音が
I've remembered it.
思い出てきたよ
Normally, when it gets to this level, it keeps coming out, but
普通このくらいになっちゃうと、 ずっと出てくるんだけど、
It's tight so it won't come out.
締まりがいいから出てこない
Okay, okay.
いい よ、
Okay.
いい よ
it hurts?
痛い?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Why does it hurt?
なんで痛いの?
I thought it would be better to delete it.
消したほうがいいと思って
Delete it once?
一回消して?
It's coming in again.
また入ってくる
I understand?
わかります?
Can I check it with my finger?
指で確かめていい?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Isn't it amazing?
すごいじゃないですか
Let's take a nice picture.
綺麗に撮っておこうね
Beautiful manpura, really.
綺麗なマンプラね、本当に
You're going to fall over, right?
よれるでしょ
Well, not at all.
まあ、全然
TRUE?
本当?
The color is also pink.
色もピンクで
The baby looks like that too.
赤ちゃんもね、あそこみたいだね
Ah so
あ そ
child?
こ?
In front of the four.
四 つの前のところ
Lower your butt.
お 尻下げてごらん
Please lower your butt further.
もっとお尻下げてごらん
That's completely wrong.
完全にやだね
You're sleepy, that face.
眠くなってるね、その顔が
You look sleepy.
眠くなってる顔ですね
Yes, right.
はい、ね
Actually, it's best to just fall asleep after finishing.
本当はね、終わった後まったいに寝ちゃうのが一番いいんですけど
hey.
ね
I had fun today too.
今日 もね、楽しくやってきました
thank you.
ありがとうございます
thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ様でした
So, let's go to the camera and Peacer.
じゃあ、カメラにピーサーに
yes.
はい
Bye bye.
バイバイね